Liudmila Sergeeva

Nationality:



Junior Frontend Developer

Russian

Address: 0468 Oslo, E-mail: sergeeva.mila.web@gmail.com

Norway **Phone:** 464 700 83

Birth date: 19.05.1985 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/liudmila-

sergeeva-927b69184

GitHub: https://github.com/MilaSergeeva

SUMMARY

In the first part of my career I worked in finance and now I want to develop myself in the field of web as a Frontend Developer. Starting in a new country motivated me to develop new skills. I made a research of Norwegian job market and saw that there is high demand for developers here. That and the fact I always were good in technologies made me even more motivated. I spent 1 year studying and developing my knowledge in coding. I want to find a place where I can grow as a specialist and be a valuable addition to the company.

Please, check my portfolio —> https://milasergeeva.github.io/portfolio/

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021.04 - now **Diversify** IT Intern

Updating current website. Working on mentorship platform.

2020 — 2021 Yandex.Praktikum Student

I have been studying at Yandex.Praktikum for 10 months. Several projects were created during this course of studies. Also I participated in some external projects which gave me great experience of working in a team and a lot of new skills. Throughout the training we were mentored by highly skilled developers. Projects:

News Explorer (the degree final project)

Full stack React application allows users find and save news. It is possible to signup and save news in users profile. Identification, authentication and authorization are realized in the app. Client-side and user-side validation, joi/celebrate modules, jwt-token. Data saves in Local Storage

Link to Repo: https://github.com/MilaSergeeva/news-explorer-frontend.git

Turbina

Collaborated with a team to create a single page application with audio-player using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Express and Node.js

Link to Repo: https://github.com/MilaSergeeva/turbina-dd

Mesto

Full-stack single page application allows users to upload, view, like and delete photos using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Express and Node.js

Link to Repo: https://github.com/MilaSergeeva/mesto-react

How to learn

Single page web site with tips on how to learn. Used HTML, CSS

Link to Repo: https://github.com/MilaSergeeva/how-to-learn

Russian travel

Single page web site with useful information about how to travel through Russia.

Link to Repo: https://github.com/MilaSergeeva/russian-travel

2015 - 2020

I have moved to Norway. After that I started to study Norwegian/passed Norskprøven exam. In 2016 I became a mother. I participated in a few NAV educational programs. I studied 3D modelling and programming on my own.

2010 - 2015

Saint-Petersburg Center of Excellence EMC

Accountant

Business Unit's forecasting and planning processes. Analyze and interpret monthly variances, trends and discrepancies between plan, actual and prior forecast in developing projections. Responsible for presenting COE's actual vs forecast expenses review to the US Finance department on a monthly basis. Track and review COE's gross and net actual/forecast.

2007 — 2010

Sole proprietor Grigor'ev (Jewelry Company)

Accountant

EDUCATION

2006 — 2010 Master's degree in Psychology

Saint-Petersburg State Institute of Psychology and Social Work

2002 — 2007 Master's degree in Economics/Management (graduated with honor)

Saint-Petersburg State University of Service & Economy

QUALIFICATIONS Systems&Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Express,

Mongoose, Git, GitHub

SAP, Oracle, 1C 8.2, Cinema 4D, Maya, Blender, AE, Coral

Draw, PS, Illustrator

PC's knowledge: Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint, Outlook

Express, working with office equipment.

Languages: Norwegian (A2)

English (Upper Intermediate)

FURTHER TRAININGS

2020/2021 Web Developer at Yandex.Praktikum

ACCA DipIFR course provided by Ernst&Young. Maya course (Polygonal modeling,

visualization and texturing, character animation in MAYA)

OTHER When I have free time I like making painting, cake design and 3D-modelling. Enjoy

travelling with my family or snowboarding with friends. Interested in other countries

and learning about their culture.